All right, Tiny. It's time to take us home with one last song.
好的 小不点 是时候最后一首歌 作为收场
I'll need the help of the finalists and all my friends.
我需要决赛选手和我所有朋友的帮助
Lou, Mr. Charlie, Miss Rose, you ready?
小露 查理先生 罗斯小姐 准备好了吗
You betcha, pup.
没错 小狗
♪ I was trying to find my way Feeling so far from home ♪
一路寻找 离家好远
♪ Then you came to me When I was all alone ♪
你奔向我 我正孤独
♪ You opened up your heart And helped me truly see ♪
打开你心 助我看到
♪ All the things that we could be ♪
一切事情 同心协力
♪ Nothing can break our bond We'll always make it through ♪
你我纽带 牢不可破 共度难关
♪ If you are by my side If you are by my side ♪ ♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你我同心  你相信我 我相信你
♪ Together there's nothing That we can't do ♪
团结一致 无坚不摧
♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你相信我 我相信你
♪ Hand in hand We'll see our whole life through ♪
手牵着手 一生共度
♪ I believe in you ♪
我相信你
♪ And you learned How to sing with feeling ♪
学会唱歌 带着感情
♪ Then you learned how to sing with soul ♪
那才真是 灵魂歌唱
♪ And you learned That when you sing from the heart ♪
你会知道 言为心声
♪ You can follow your dreams ♪
跟随梦想
♪ 'Cause friends are always there For you ♪
因为朋友 永远守候
♪ Tried and true ♪
试过才知
♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你相信我 我相信你
♪ Together there's nothing That we can't do ♪
团结一致 无坚不摧
♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你相信我 我相信你
♪ Hand in hand We'll make it through ♪
手牵着手 共度难关
♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你相信我 我相信你
♪ Together there's nothing That we can't do ♪
团结一致 无坚不摧
♪ When you believe in me And I believe in you ♪
你相信我 我相信你
♪ Hand in hand We'll sing our whole life through ♪
手牵着手 一生共度
♪ I believe in you ♪
我相信你